OLE WORSLEY

☑ cole.s.worsley@gmail.com 9708196405 Denver, CO in coleworsley coleworsley

SUMMARY

I am a hard working front end web developer with a passion for learning. I have a well-rounded foundation in test driven development and object oriented programming. I'm driven to work with a strong development team to learn and grow as well as create a quality product. With a background in financial analytics, I also bring strong business experience and attention to detail.

SKILLS

Technical: JavaScript (ES6), React/Redux, ¡Query, HTML5, CSS3, Node / Express, Knex / Postgresql, Sketch, Excel VBA, Jest / Enzyme, Mocha / Chai

EXPERIENCE

Turing School of Software and Design

Denver, CO

Front-End Engineering Student

Mar 2017 - Sep 2017

Construct functional web applications with Javascript, CSS, and HTML over a seven month intensive web development program. Program covers primarily client side applications with focuses on Test Driven Development, UI/UX, and pair programming.

Centura Health Physician Group

Denver, CO

Sr. Financial Analyst

Aug 2016 - Mar 2017

Responsible for tracking growth and communicating results to hospital leadership for entire north Denver region.

Financial Analyst

Sep 2013 - Aug 2016

Utilize excel and VBA to design and build reporting package for physician group financial and operational analysis.

Credit Analyst Intern

Jun 2013 - Sep 2013

Developed a business acumen in teamwork and communication along with a fundamental understanding of Microsoft Excel and the use of information systems attributed to Electronic Medical Records.

PROJECTS

Movie Tracker

A website implemented with React and Redux similar to IMDB. This was a four person project placing a large emphasis on well established git workflow and team dynamics. We also utilized get, post, and delete requests to manage data in a prebuilt node.js server and fetch those requests to our client side application.

Swapi Box

A project that returns nested asynchronous promises from the Star Wars API to display on the DOM through React. Emphasis was on using the fetch API and integration testing using fetch mock.

Weatherly

Project built on React.js using the Weather Underground API to display a detailed weather forecast. For this project, we implemented asynchronous Javascript to load various components and information onto the page. It also includes a custom built prefix search trie to load different locations to send to the API.

EDUCATION

University of Denver

BS Finance 2013

Awarded the Brad Busse full endowed scholarship for exemplary performance as a division one swimmer and as a student.